http://www.coatech.co.uk/privacy-policy

Call us: 01745 887381
HomeCommercialResin Bound SurfacingResin Bonded SurfacingResin TreepitsDecorative FlakeDecorative Recycled GlassDecorative QuartzSelf SmoothersMMAIndustrialResin CoatingsSelf SmoothersChemical Resistant ScreedsFast-Cure Cementitious ScreedsMMARubber Crumb & MulchCar ParksAbout usEnvironmentHealth & SafetyWhat makes us differentLatest NewsBlogCareersCase StudiesContact Us
Privacy Policy
At Coatech we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors.
This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site.
We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.
Information We Collect
In running and maintaining our website we may collect and process the following data about you:
i.	Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.
ii.	Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you register for information or request a sample.
iii.	Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.
Use of Cookies
Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a visitor. We may use cookies where appropriate to gather information about your computer in order to assist us in improving our website. We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie.
Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computer’s hard drive. Such information will not identify you personally. It is statistical data. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever. You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish.
This can easily be done by activating the reject cookies setting on your computer. Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.
Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.
Use of Your Information
We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you.
In addition to this we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:
i.	To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.
ii.	To provide information to you relating to other products that may be of interest to you. Such additional information will only be provided where you have consented to receive such information.
iii.	To inform you of any changes to our website, services or goods and products.If you have previously used our services we may provide to you details of services, or other services, that you may be interested in.
We will not pass on your personal information to third parties without your consent
Storing Your Personal Data
Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically, sending such information is entirely at your own risk.
Disclosing Your Information
We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:
i.	In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.
ii.	Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.
iii.	To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.Third Party Links
On occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site’s policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data.
Access to Information
In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 you have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you.
Contacting Us
Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy by emailing info@coatech.co.uk, or calling us on 01745 887381
What next?
If you require any other assistance we are happy to answer any questions. Please
call us on 01745 887381 or request a call back.
Connect with us
Sign up for Newsletter
Unsubscribe
Enter your Email Address
Email:
Unsubscribe
Cancel
Join Our Mailing Lists
Please fill your details in below.
Please select which mailing lists you would like to join.
Unit 4, Bridge Business Park, Marsh Road, Rhyl, Denbighshire, LL18 2QA
